RASYID KUSNADY

Sleman, ID | P: +62 85842688724 | rasyidkusnady@mail.ugm.ac.id | linkedin.com/in/rasyid-kusnady-25214b218/

SUMMARY

I am an undergraduate student majoring in Software Engineering at Gadjah Mada University and have been working for about 2 Years as a Programmer, especially as a Mobile Software Developer. I like to make connections with everyone in the community and am easily adapt to both socially and at work. I always develop myself in hard skills or soft skills. I can do teamwork or individual work. I'm interested in technology especially software engineering, artificial intelligence, and internet of things.

EXPERIENCE

FREELANCE PROGRAMMER - Sleman, Indonesia

Freelance

November 2021 - Present

- Tech Stack: Java, Python, C++, C#, Arduino, Firebase, MySQL
- Made some Mobile applications.
- Fixed Bugs and QA Tests.
- · Added new feature in the project.

BIT TECHNOLOGY - Sleman, Indonesia

Co-Founder, Chief Operating Officer, and Programmer

August 2020 - September 2021

- Tech Stack: Java, Python, Solidity, Blockchain, Javascript, MySQL, AWS, CorelDraw, Photoshop.
- Made Social Media strategy and Campaign for DenganKitaAja.
- Organized Team in the project.
- Research and Development products for sustainable business.
- Made COVCHAIN for tracking vaccines with blockchain technologies.

PT KEDATA INDONESIA DIGITAL- Sleman, Indonesia

Intern, Data Scientist and Graphic Designer

July 2020 - December 2020

- Tech Stack: R Programming, Python Programming, Javascript, Statistics, Photoshop.
- Made data analytics about some products on Instagram.
- Scrapped and collected data from eCommerce.
- Processed data and made analytics for Kotabaru Election.
- Created a Social Media strategy for the Election Campaign.

KARANG TARUNA TRIMULYO- Sleman, Indonesia

Staff, Public Relations

July 2018 - Present

- Communicated with the member and agency in the event.
- Invited sub-group to attend the event.

EDUCATION

GADJAH MADA UNIVERSITY - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Jul 2022 - present

Bachelor of Applied Science - Software Engineering

SMK NEGERI 2 DEPOK - Sleman, Indonesia

Informatics System, Network, and Application, 4 years program

July 2017 - Jun 2021

ACHIEVEMENT

3RD PLACE IN VIDEO COMPETITION - FIB UGM

October 2018

Video comptetition "Jogja Bebas Klitih"

2ND PLACE IN KEJURDA Pelajar Cabang Olahraga BRIDGE – DIKPORA D.I. Yogyakarta BRIDGE SPORT

July 2019

2ND PLACE Kejuaraan BRIDGE Terbuka Rektor UNSOED – Universitas Jendral Soedirman October 2019 BRIDGE SPORT

2ND PLACE IN LKS Software Applications for Business – DIKPORA D.I.Yogyakarta

November 2019

Skill Competition between vocational high school in Yogyakarta, Tech: VB.NET and MSSQL

3RD PLACE IN POPDA DIY Cabang Olahraga BRIDGE – DIKPORA D.I.Yogyakarta

March 2020
BRIDGE SPORT Nomor Beregu Putra

3RD PLACE IN POPDA DIY Cabang Olahraga BRIDGE – DIKPORA D.I.Yogyakarta

March 2020
BRIDGE SPORT Nomor Beregu Campuran

3ND PLACE IN KEJURNAS BRIDGE – GABSI PUSAT

BRIDGE SPORT nomor beregu campuran

July 2020

2ND PLACE IN JAKBEE HACKATHON – Baznas DKI Jakarta

November 2021

Mobile Android App for mitigation. Tech: Java Mobile.

ADDITIONAL

Technical: JavaScript, Python, Java, Kotlin, PHP, VB.NET, Arduino, C#, NodeJS, MySQL, MongoDB, Git **Soft skills**: Problem Solving, Public Speaking.

Interest: Mobile Software Development, Web Development, Blockchain, Data Science, Machine Learning, Internet of Things.